Contactar

gab_villacis@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/gabriel-villacis (LinkedIn)

www.gabrielvillacis.com (Blog)

Certifications

Scrum Developer Professional Ethical Hacking Software Design and Architecture Specialization

Gabriel Villacis

Technical Lead | Software Architect | Cloud Native Technologies Expert | Machine Learning Enthusiast | Java, Scala, JS, C# & Python Guayaquil

Extracto

Software Engineering senior professional with more than 9 years of experience leading the design and implementation of mission-critical software solutions for industries such as: banking, commerce, marketing and telecommunications.

I am currently focused on the design of distributed systems and reactive systems based on microservices and event-driven architectures, adopting the DevOps culture and the use of cloud native technologies such as: Spring Webflux, Spring Cloud, Camunda, Kafka, Docker, Kubernetes and AWS.

Experiencia

Eclipsoft S.A.

3 años 3 meses

Technical Lead septiembre de 2021 - Present (11 meses)

Guayaquil

Software Architect

mayo de 2019 - agosto de 2021 (2 años 4 meses)

Guayaquil

EELA

Python Instructor julio de 2021 - Present (1 año 1 mes)

Guayaquil, Guayas, Ecuador

Sociedad Ecuatoriana de Estadística MLOps Instructor julio de 2021 - Present (1 año 1 mes)

Guayaquil, Guayas, Ecuador

Deporpas S.A.
Software Architect
febrero de 2017 - marzo de 2019 (2 años 2 meses)
Guayaquil, Guayas, Ecuador

Banco Territorial S.A.
Software Engineer
mayo de 2013 - noviembre de 2016 (3 años 7 meses)
Guayaquil, Guayas, Ecuador

Educación

Universidad de Guayaquil Ingeniería, Ingeniería en Sistemas Computacionales